Russian Slavic Central Asian Student Association Records MS271
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Russian Slavic Central Asian Student Association Records
2019 -- 2021
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
MS271
12 Digital Object(s)
166 Megabytes
This collection contains event ideas and fliers, budgets, the constitution, logo, and club fair presentation created by the Russian Slavic Central Asian Student Association (RSCA).
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by Ashley Aron, 2021, accession number MS-2021-030.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in one series, 2021 accessions.
Biographical / Historical
The Russian Circle was established in the early to mid-1990s and renamed the Russian Slavic Students Association (RSSA) in approximately 2014. In 2020, RSSA was renamed the Russian Slavic Central Asian Student Association (RSCA). Its mission is to provide students with opportunities to become more familiar with Russian culture, language, history, society, and politics. The RSCA is the only Slavic/Soviet/post-Soviet cultural group at Tufts and is endorsed by the Russian Language and Cultural Studies Program through the Department of International Literary and Cultural Studies.
The Russian Slavic Central Asian Student Association's events and meetings are located in the Russian House on 101 Talbot Ave. The Russian House houses eight undergraduate students in their second to fourth year.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains event ideas and fliers, budgets, the constitution, logo, and club fair presentation created by the Russian Slavic Central Asian Student Association (RSCA).
Student life
- 2021 accessions, 2019 -- 2021; MS271.000001; 166 Megabytes; 12 Digital Object(s)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred by Ashley Aron, 2021, accession MS-2021-030.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains event ideas and fliers, budgets, the constitution, logo, and club fair presentation created by the Russian Slavic Central Asian Student Association (RSCA).
  - COVID modified event schedule, 2020 -- 2021; MS271.000002; 17.01 Kilobytes
  - Differences between Russian Slavic Central Asian Student Association, Russian House, and Russian Program, 2019; MS271.000003; 16.38 Kilobytes
  - Experimental Russian Slavic Central Asian event ideas, 2020 -- 2021; MS271.000004; 12.74 Kilobytes
  - Russian House Fletcher Speaker Series event poster, circa 2019 -- 2021; MS271.000005; 250.82 Kilobytes
  - Budget, 2019 -- 2020; MS271.000010; 10.69 Kilobytes
  - Russian Slavic Central Asian Student Association Club Fair presentation, 2020; MS271.000007; 164.98 Megabytes
  - Russian Slavic Central Asian Student Association logo, circa 2019 -- 2021; MS271.000008; 91.62 Kilobytes
  - Social hour poster, 2020; MS271.000009; 226.07 Kilobytes
  - Budget, 2020 -- 2021; MS271.000006; 30.13 Kilobytes
  - Russian Music Festival poster, 2020; MS271.000011; 561.32 Kilobytes
  - Russian Slavic Central Asian Student Association poster, circa 2019 -- 2021; MS271.000012; 567.65 Kilobytes
  - Russian Slavic Central Asian Students Assocation Constitution, circa 2019 -- 2021; MS271.000013; 17.19 Kilobytes